ALLAH-O AKBAR
ALHAMDULILLAH.
We praise God.
WA ASHHADU AN LA ILAHA ILLA ALLAH, WAHDAHU LA SHAREEKA LAH.
I was hoping today that the sermon would be given by General Spooner, but he didn't make it yet. He'll be here tonight.
Meanwhile, I'm stuck. Cause he graduates this morning... he graduated this morning, 4 hours ago.
And I was hoping I was gonna catch him to tell us about his experiences in the Marines.
I don't know if he'll call me sir when he comes here. On the telephone he said no way!
And I notice we have a new member. She just joined us. And her name is Rashide, by the way.
That's a dangerous name these days. Salman Rushdie, and Rashad Khalifa. Now, we have Rashide. What's your first name? What do they...
Hafiza
Hafiza?
Rashada
Rashada? Rashada. Oh, that's even more dangerous.
Rashada is the first name? The middle name. The first name is Hafiza. Hafiza Rashada.
We welcome the new member to the masjid.
Mahvash, will you push that door? The noise will...
So, I'm stuck to give this KHUTBAH and I have no idea what I'm gonna talk about, but I... I put down...this will help me a lot.
This is something that I distributed last week and I will just go through it with you. It is the May issue of the Muslim Perspective
which reminds me that month of Ramadan begins on April 7th. So, I congratulate you because this is a big feast for the soul.
We'll spend the whole day fasting which means you'll be remembering God. And your soul, in one month, will fulfill one of the 5 pillars of Islam.
I think, inadvertently, it is also a feast for the body. Every Friday, we have that, A feast here. An international potluck every Friday in Ramadan.
So, this is just to give you some psychological preparation before the Ramadan is here. The issue of May 1989 of the Perspective
is... the main title is why did God send his messenger, now? And we read in SURA number 2 verse 151, that among
the ways God perfects His favor on us is to send a messenger to recite God's revelations, God's new information to us
and new wisdom that He adds to our intellect. I'm trying to remember the verse and to teach us new things. This is verse 151 of SURA 2.
In SURA 43, we read the modes of communication between God and us; how does God communicate with the human beings.
And we are given 3 different ways. The first one is direct inspiration, that God inspires you directly to do something.
You're just walking about, going about your life, normally and God inspires you to do something, directly.
The other method is from behind a barrier like when God spoke to Moses through the burning bush.
God... God... only God's voice was felt by Moses. Moses didn't see God. He could not see God, but he heard God's voice.
And the third method is to send a messenger to disperse the information, God's... through the messenger, God will send a lot of
information. These are the three modes. Now, this issue's one year later after the big announcement, last year.
And, why did God send his messenger, now? The answer as taken from verse 151 of SURA 2. Cause God loves you and wants to save you.
And I give here some major reasons for sending God's messenger of the Covenant. Number 1 is that the vast majority of human beings
are yet to come to this world. If you recall, I put in the introduction and may be still hanging there
a graph showing how many people came to this world and how many will come between now and the end of the world.
And I projected that 70 million... 70 billion people will come to this world between now and the end of the world while only
6 billion came from the time of Adam until now. So, the people who will show up between now and the end of the world are 14 times as
many as the people who came in the past. So, God is putting the message together, the message of all the prophets together. As we
see in SURA 3 verse 81. All the prophets came. All the prophets delivered the scriptures. The Quran was the last scripture
through Muhammad, the last prophet. The last message-bearing messenger was Muhammad. And
after all... all of them have come and all the messages have been delivered, God tells us in SURA 3 verse 81 that He will send
a messenger to put all these together in one and crystalize, purify - this a chemical term by the way - crystallization is the highest form of
purification of any material. And this came inadvertently, but it's to put the messages together represented to this
vast majority of the world. Vast majority of people. Number 2, the pure Quran that God intends for the world never existed.
Think about that. The pure Quran never existed. When the prophet Muhammad died, what did he leave?
He left the Quran written with his own hand in the chronological sequence. In other words, if you open the first page,
he had SURA IQRA at the beginning, not Al-Fãtehah. The first revelation was there.
And besides it was the instructions as to where it goes in the final Quran that God intends for the world.
And then, the whole book was written down in that chronological sequence. The last SURA revealed was SURA 110
when God's victory comes
(110:1) إِذَا جَآءَ نَصْرُ ٱللَّهِ وَٱلْفَتْحُ
And then the prophet died only a few months after that.
And he left the Quran in that chronological sequence which is not the sequence intended for the world.
Abubakr came and he was busy with the wars of reversion. People reverted from Islam and rebelled against him.
And so did Omar, also. And after Omar came Uthman. Omar had expanded the Muslim world beyond Arabia.
And it became necessary to write down the Quran in the right order that God intends for the world. So, Uthman appointed a committee
to carry out the prophet's instructions. They took that original copy in the chronological sequence and they read the instructions and
they put the Quran together in the sequence that we have today starting with Al-Fãtehah and ending with SURA Al-Naas.
Now, Satan did not leave them alone. When they finished... now the last revelation before SURA Al-Nassr was SURA... SURA
last SURA revealed in Medina was SURA number 9
So, after they finished, they said yeah, let's go celebrate. Somebody said hey, let's add a couple of verses to honor the prophet.
So, they added those two verses. And I think you know the story very well. And so, the Quran was written down with two extraneous
verses in it. Two satanic verses. Satan had to put his... his seed there. And they stayed there suspected
And all the believers I know were all suspicious of these two verses. They didn’t like them. They didn’t fit text-wise, meaning-wise
with the Quran. So, for the first time, next month, IN SHA ALLAH, the Quran will be restored. So, this is another reason, another major reason
for sending a messenger, now that the pure Quran that God intends for the world never existed. It will exist for the first time
next month, IN SHA ALLAH.
Number 3, Islam has been distorted by the Muslims into a Satanic cult. The Islam around the world, you can see, you can tell
from what they're doing. I think I announced today that they know now the person who put the bomb on Pan American flight
where 270 innocent people died and that person is quote, unquote a Muslim. He made the whole world angry. He gave Islam a bad name.
We know what Khomeini is doing to the freedom of expression, speaking in the name of an Islamic Republic, a Muslim leader
and we know what Ben Baz say about the Earth being flat. They're just setting all the examples that Satan wants to set for a religion.
It turned into a Satanic cult. According to their religion, which is no longer has anything to do with the Prophet Mohammad
you kill the person who does not pray the 5 daily prayers, you kill the person who drinks alcohol for the 4th time, you kill the adulterers
you kill the person who reverted, according to the measures from Islam. So, this takes care of 99.99% of the Muslim world itself. Kill, kill, kill.
And, this is... this justifies why they could kill any time they want to cause according to their laws, there is always a reason to kill
somebody. Just give me anybody, and I give you a reason to kill them.
That's a Satanic cult. Number 4, the Muslims are doing everything wrong in defiance of the Quran.
For example, I put this under number 6. They do the call to prayer, AZAN, wrong.
You know they say
اشهد ان لا اله
الله اکبر - الله اکبر - اشهد ان لا اله الا الله - اشهد ان محمد رسول الله
Right there
they already violated the commandment that the mosque belongs to God. You should mention God's name only in your practices of worship
and depends on where you are, you can also go on
اشهد ان علی ولی الله
اشهد ان اهل البیت حجه الله
So, it all depends on where you are, but either way there is not a single mosque in the Muslim world
that follows this commandment that the mosque belongs to God, you shall mention only God's name.
Number 7, they do their ablution wrong and if you don't believe it, ask Abdullah when waiting in line for ablution in Turkey.
You know, the people have already started the prayer and these people are going through their 9 steps of ablution
trying to get every hair, you know, because there is a hadith that says... there's a hadith that says if you leave a hair dry
it will go to hell. They separate this hair or something, sending it to hell. So, they make sure that everything is wet.
Number 8, they do their contact prayers, the SALAT, wrong. God says in SURA 20
(20:14) أَقِمِ ٱلصَّلَوٰةَ لِذِكْرِىٓ
Singular. Observe the contact prayer to commemorate Me. Singular.
But all of them, they mention Muhammad, ALE Muhammad, Ibrahim, ALE Ibrahim, Muhammad and his family. Abraham and his family.
in their contact prayers. And this is by definition polytheism or SHIRK, idol worship.
Number 9, they do their ZAKAT, obligatory charity, wrong. According to their laws, now, they give their charity
2.5% of your savings above 50 dollars that are one year old, once a year. This is the law of charity over there
which means the poor will die of starvation by the time you do that. Now, if you look in the Quran
in SURA 6, we learn that charity must go out whenever you receive money. Any money that enters your pocket and is yours, the net
you take 2.5% out of every 100 dollars. 2.5 dollars, you give them away to your relatives not to anybody else.
This is the ZAKAT, the obligatory charity. If you wanna build a school or a mosque or a hospital, that is general charity. That's something else.
But 2.5% of your net income must go to the poor immediately. Which means a continuous flow of money from people to the relatives
their parents and their cousins and their sisters and brothers and so on. That's the correct way of doing ZAKAT.
And the Quran gives the ZAKAT so much importance, God says My mercy encompasses all things, but I will designate it for those who give the ZAKAT.
So, this shows, in other words, if you don't give the ZAKAT, you're out of God's mercy. It is very important and they don't do it.
Number 10, they do the fasting of Ramadan wrong. Just watch what they're starting fasting in the other place.
They never start on the right day. They never end on the right day because a hadith says you must see the moon with your eyes.
Well, if you see the moon with your eyes, it's too late. It's already past the time.
And then, they turn into the most obnoxious creatures during fasting, they become on being hungry and thirsty
almost fighting.
You're supposed to be the nicest person during Ramadan because you don't wanna nullify your efforts.
When you're driving in the street, you're not gonna rush in front of somebody. You don't wanna offend anyone
because you're very careful not to ruin your fasting. All that month, you're the nicest person in the world to everybody.
Number 11, they do their Hajj pilgrimage wrong at the wrong time. Pilgrimage, in the Quran, is month, 4 months. Not one day.
The government of Saudi Arabia want you to do it in one day and get it over with. Get them out of here. But it is supposed to be 4 months.
How do you jam 2 million people in one city in one day? Well, you can imagine, you know.
You can imagine... when I did the pilgrimage with my parents, I told them you stay here. Then, I'll do it on your behalf.
Certain things were in the crowds. Because they will die. People die. They're trampled under the feet.
And they have the stoning of Satan's ceremony or whatever. They're just gruesome. I was worried about myself.
Also, they ruin the pilgrimage by going to visit the prophet's tomb. The prophet is not there. Not even his dust is there anymore.
They go... I don't know what they go for. And I wrote in the Perspective, you know, tear down the prophet's tomb.
And some fanatic Saudi Arabian, very angry, very hot called and left a message on the telephone machine trying to prove that
the prophet is not buried in his mosque. He's buried in his house. So, there's a hadith that said
There's a hadith, ironically, that the prophet said God cursed the Jews and the Christians because they made their prophets'
tombs into mosques which is not really the case. The case is the opposite. The Muslims are the ones who did that.
So, he was trying to convince me that the prophet is buried in his house, but it's the people who put the house in his mosque.
in a mosque. So, either way, the Muslims are wrong in their pilgrimage.
Number 12, I put, if the Muslims continue as they are, they will go to hell. OK. So, these are some of the major reasons.
Why now... Just look at yourself and myself when we were doing the SALAT wrong and the fasting wrong and the ZAKAT wrong.
And God is looking at us. If He cared about you, would He not send somebody to correct you or some instructions, somehow?
If He really loves you, He will say hey you're doing this wrong. You're not making contact with Me. You're wasting your time.
This is how you do it right.
So, verse 151 of SURA 2 explains that. I'm perfecting My blessings on you by sending a messenger.
And this is throughout the times. But now especially, when you look at all this
because God really loves the people and is giving them a chance to redeem themselves, He did not just sit and watch them go wrong.
God decided to send corrections to you and to me and so... so, we don't waste our time. Obviously, God knew
that we are sincere. We are seeking Him. We want to worship Him. And we want to redeem ourselves. And obviously, we deserve
these instructions, but God says that in the Quran that He knows the innermost thoughts and accordingly, He guides
the people who deserve to be guided and He keeps away the people who don't deserve to be guided.
I am mentioning in the front of page of this issue that as detailed on page 2, every single reason listed above is supported by irrefutable
physical evidence from the Quran and from its formidable mathematical code. Then, at the bottom, I put another note
during the last 12 months, I presented overwhelming Quranic mathematical proofs that I am God's messenger of the Covenant.
and NOT a single Muslim scholar came up with a single reason why I could not be God's messenger. Their silence is very significant.
Why can't they come up with one reason?
TUBU ILLA ALLAH, repent.
ALHAMDULILLAH. We praise God.
WA ASHHADU AN LA ILAHA ILLA ALLAH, WAHDAHU LA SHAREEKA LAH.
And I bear witness that there is no god except the one God.
With this second year, the new year... the first year was rather harsh just to shake somebody and to warn them and wake them up.
But IN SHA ALLAH, we will enter into a period of... of love and tranquility and compassion and we'll see
hopefully, it will work to save a few people. There will be no more anger cause we did the work.
In the last... in the last many years in the past, we started out by being very nice and it didn’t work. And then, I got louder and louder.
But this... this is the way, God wants it if you see the Quran and the sequence of the progression of the message.
It is simply because you see somebody... there's a big ditch here. And somebody's going to fall in it. So,
you first say hey! you're gonna fall in the ditch. But the person doesn’t hear you and keeps going towards the ditch.
You're gonna shout louder. Hey! you're gonna fall in the ditch. If he ignores you, maybe, he's deaf. Then, you start to get physical.
You'll go there and try to pull him. You're trying to save him. So, but this is how the progression is.
Now, the Quran tells us. Let me get a Quran and share a couple of verses with you.
43:21
The response to every messenger was this. What they said was we found our parents doing this and we simply follow their footsteps.
They don’t want to change what they inherited from their parents. Thus, whenever We sent a warner to any community,
the leaders said we found our parents following certain practices and we are following their footsteps.
In other words, we don’t want to change.
The messenger would say what if I showed you better guidance than that of your parents?
They said we reject whatever you bring. Consequently, We punished them. Note the consequences for the rejectors.
It seems in the Quran that this always happens. And we are certainly seeing it although not as bad as in the past, actually
as I will share with you in a few moments. In SURA 23, verse 44
Then, We sent our messengers in succession. Every time a community received their messenger, they rejected him. Every time.
And this is past tense. Consequently, We annihilated them one after the other and We turned them into history.
Doomed are the people who do not believe. In SURA 40, verse 5
Rebelling before them were the people of Noah and communities after them. Every generation persecuted their messenger
seeking to neutralize him and they argued with falsehood to make it dominate the truth, but I overtook them. How terrible
was My retribution.
So, this seems to be the general trend. There's something different this time.
I'm slowing down for Mohtasham and Frank to come back.
In the end of SURA 40, we read the following verses. When their messengers went to them with clear revelations or clear miracles
or clear signs, they were satisfied with the knowledge they had. They said this is what we like. This is what we know now.
The very thing they ridiculed caused their doom. Then, when they saw our retribution, they said now we believe in God alone
and we reject the idols we have set up. But it's too late. See, once the retribution is here, it is too late. But alas their belief is no longer
useful once they see Our retribution. This is God's system that is never changeable. The disbelievers are always losers.
Now, we see throughout the Quran. I don’t need to go through these verses with you. But we see guarantees of victory for the believers
and for the messengers, God's messengers. And especially, in the last SURA of the Quran, last SURA revealed chronologically.
which says when God's victory comes and you the people embracing God's religion in great numbers.
This SURA consists of 19 words. And the first verse consists of 19 letters which means what? Means this is intended for us.
And from all signs that this message of worshiping God alone, people are receptive everywhere in the world, all over the world.
There are so many people. I'm really surprised how receptive people are. And you can see the sincerity in their writings, their letters
their telephone calls, in their behavior. I mean, I don’t think it ever happened before in history that in the lifetime of the messenger
he delivered the message to this... this many people. Certainly, never. I mean, the message, this message, worshiping God alone
upholding the Quran alone has been delivered to more people than the people that Noah, Abraham, Moses, Jesus and Zachariah
and John and all these people delivered in their lifetime combined multiplied many times over. I'm talking about just the delivery
of the message. But the people who believed are overwhelmingly even more. You know how many people were with Jesus when
he... when he finished... when he completed his message. He had a dozen of people... a dozen people.
And you see in our conference, we have hundreds of people. ALHAMDULILLAH. And this last conference were 150 people
approximately. And these are sincere believers. I mean, I screened them. There may be two or three exceptions there.
But these are really people who believed in worshiping God alone, devoting their worship to God alone. They corrected their practices.
And they uphold the Quran alone. So, this is really victory. And we should be thankful to God that...
that it is not any more popular than this. I don’t know how to put this but because we'll have... we will have no time to do anything else
but as it is, we have time now to get the translation out, to get the principles out, to get the information out.
And we don’t need any secret service or crowds out in the street or anything like that.
I believe that every messenger's really for the future generations not for his generation.
But all these people who are... this is very pleasing to our hearts to see so many people now believing and worshiping God alone.
And this is the criterion that tells you that you are right. Because the Quran said that every party is happy and pleased
with what they. And we have to... to... to examine ourselves as to are we right or wrong? Are we fooling ourselves?
So, your criterion is with your worshiping God alone, upholding the Quran alone.
AQEM AL-SALAT
ALLAH-O AKBAR. ALLAH-O AKBAR.